[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "We get this word from the name of an infamous hangman.", "correct_answer": "derrick", "incorrect_answers": ["crane", "tontine", "guillotine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the parody Epic Movie, which character comes from the movie Snakes on a Plane?", "correct_answer": "Susan", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter", "Rachel", "Edwardo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He is best known for the role of Capt. Cragen on Law and Order: SVU.", "correct_answer": "Dann Florek", "incorrect_answers": ["Ice-T", "Richard Belzer", "Gavin McCloud"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what city was the popular TV series EastEnders set?", "correct_answer": "London", "incorrect_answers": ["San Francisco", "Los Angeles", "New York"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the group of whole numbers under addition, what is the additive identity of 7?", "correct_answer": "0", "incorrect_answers": ["1/7", "1", "-7"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Cheech and Chongs movie Up In Smoke, Tom Skerrit plays Cheechs cousin, Strawberry. What did Cheech tell Chong not to do, before he introduced him to Strawberry?", "correct_answer": "Not to stare at his birthmark", "incorrect_answers": ["Not to talk to the talking bird", "Not to touch his bong collection", "Not to mention Vietnam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is no difference between blanching and parboiling.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are all galaxies contained within according to the final scene of the 1997 comedy Men in Black?", "correct_answer": "Marbles", "incorrect_answers": ["Embryos heads", "The eye of an alien", "A fleas stomach"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are cases of heterosexual men wearing bras to hide his enlarged chest.  What is the name of the disease that causes this hormonal defect?", "correct_answer": "Gynecomastia", "incorrect_answers": ["Hepatitis", "Budd-Chiari Syndrome", "Caroli Disease"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which vegetables come in the Enterprise Java flavour?", "correct_answer": "Beans", "incorrect_answers": ["Broccoli", "Potatoes", "Peas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a heart valve?", "correct_answer": "Carotid Valve", "incorrect_answers": ["Tricuspid valve", "Mitral Valve", "Pulmonary Valve"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did Colorado become a state?", "correct_answer": "1876", "incorrect_answers": ["1796", "1896", "1776"]}]